
import { contAgain,dataOutput} from '../../js/source.js'


let Flamingo = [{
    name: "Flamingo",
    answer : "",
    question:"",
},
    {
        "question": "What had been put up on the bulletin-board?",
        "answer": "The French districts of Alsace and Lorraine had been taken over by the Prussians. Hence, the bulletin board displayed the news that an order had come from Berlin to teach only German in the schools of Alsace and Lorraine."
    },
    {
        "question": "The people in this story suddenly realise how precious their language is to them. What shows you this? Why does this happen?",
        "answer": "He asked his fellow Frenchmen to protect their language as it is like a key to the prison they were about to be in. This made the people realize how precious their language was to them. This also shows the people's love for their country and culture which is reflected through their love for the French language."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was Franz expected to be prepared with for school that day?",
        "answer": " Franz was expected to be prepared with the use of 'Participles' that day. His teacher M. Hamel had said that he would question the children on participles"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is Saheb happy working at the tea-stall? Explain.",
        "answer": "No, Saheb is not happy working at the tea-stall. He is no longer his own master. His face has lost the carefree look. The steel canister seems heavier than the plastic bag he would carry with ease earlier."
    },
    {
        "question": "What makes the city of Firozabad famous?",
        "answer": "The city of Firozabad is famous for its bangles. Every other family in Firozabad is engaged in making bangles. It is the centre of India's glass-blowing industry. Families have spent generations working around furnaces, welding glass, making bangles for the women in the land."
    },
    {
        "question": "Mention the hazards of working in the glass bangles industry.",
        "answer": "Glass blowing, welding and soldering pieces of glass are all health hazards. Even the dust from polishing the glass of bangles adversely affects the eyes and even adults go blind. Thus, the surroundings, prevailing conditions and the type of job involved-all prove risky to the health of the workers"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the “misadventure ” that William Douglas speaks about?  ",
        "answer": "The “misadventure” that William Douglas speaks about is the one where he was thrown into a swimming pool by an older boy. He found it difficult to breathe and almost drowned. He made three unsuccessful attempts to jump out of the water. He would have drowned if someone hadn't brought him out of the water."
    },
    {
        "question": "How did Douglas overcome his fear of water? ",
        "answer": " Douglas' journey of truly overcoming his fear to its tiniest vestiges began. He swam alone in the pool. He went to Lake Wentworth to dive. He tried every possible stroke he learnt. Finally, in his diving expedition, in the Warm Lake, he conquered his fear completely."
    },
    {
        "question": "What made the peddler think that he had indeed fallen into a rattrap?",
        "answer": "The peddler considered the whole world as a big rattrap, its sole purpose being to set baits for people. The joys and riches of this world are nothing but tempting baits and anyone who is tempted by them was captured by the rattrap which completely closed in on him."
    },

    {
        "question": " Why was Edla happy to see the gift left by the peddler?  ",
        "answer": "Edla showed great trust in him by letting him stay at their manor on the Christmas Eve. But the news about the robbery had left her dejected. So she was overjoyed when she reached home to find the package and the letter left by the peddler. This gesture of appreciation from the peddler made her happy."
    },
    {
        "question": "Draw the character sketch of the peddler ? [The Rattrap]  ",
        "answer": "Instead of flowing some goodness in him, he had the human weakness of petty thievery and begging to keep his body and soul together. He wore rags and hunger gleamed in his eyes. He went round selling self-made small rattrape of wire. Devoid of any sheltering place, he could spend his night wherever he desired. Mostly he came across sour faces and was a victim of his cruel circumstances. He could of knock at the door any person for his night shelter. "
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did Gandhi agree to a settlement of 25 per cent refund to the farmers? ",
        "answer": "He wanted the poor farmers to realise that they too had rights and that they need not really live in fear of the British landlords. Therefore, although he had initially quoted a 50 percent refund, he later agreed to a settlement of 25 percent refund to the farmers. Besides, Gandhi was interested in long-term solutions rather than immediate benefits"
    },
    {
        "question": "How was Gandhi able to influence lawyers? Give instances? ",
        "answer": "Gandhi asked the lawyers what they would do if he was sentenced to prison. They said that they had come to advise him. If he went to jail, they would go home. Then Gandhi asked them about the injustice to the sharecroppers. The lawyers held consultations. They came to the conclusion that it would be shameful desertion if they went home. So, they told Gandhi that they were ready to follow him into jail."
    },
    {
        "question": "What work did the 'office boy' do in the Gemini Studios, Why did he join the studios? Why was he disappointed?",
        "answer": "The office boy used to apply makeup on the actors who were part of the crowd in a film. He would mix paint in a large vessel and apply, rather literally slap them on their faces. He was a poet too. He joined the studios with a dream to become a star or a screenwriter or a lyrics writer. He was disappointed because he couldn’t achieve any of it and stayed in the same position as an office boy."
    },
    {
        "question": "]Did the people at Gemini Studios have any particular political affiliations?  ",
        "answer": "Most people at Gemini Studios were followers of Gandhiji. They didn’t have other political affiliations. However, there were strong opposers of communism."
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the Boss of Gemini Studios?",
        "answer": "Poets And Pancakes. Who was The Boss of Gemini Studios? The Boss of the Gemini Studios was Mr. S.S."
    },

    {
        "question": "Why was Kothamangalam Subbu considered No. 2 in Gemini Studios? ",
        "answer": " Kothamangalam Subbu succeeded in securing the place closest to The Boss by means of flattery. He was not brilliant but a rather cheerful person and exceedingly loyal to The Boss. He offered solutions whenever The Boss was in a fix. Thus, the other employees considered him No."
    },
    {
        "question": "Why do most celebrity writers despise being interviewed?  ",
        "answer": "Celebrity writers believe that interviews unduly interfere in their private lives. They regard themselves as victims of interviews. They claim that the interview in some way 'diminishes' them, just like some ancient cultures believed that a portrait of a person takes away his soul"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do you think Umberto Eco likes being interviewed? Give reasons for your opinion.",
        "answer": "Yes, Umberto Eco, in all possibilities, likes being interviewed. He readily answers every question asked by Mukund Padmanabhan in an energetic and lively manner. He does not seem apprehensive about sharing his secrets, experiences and opinions with the interviewer, and consequently, the world."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where was it most likely that the two girls would find work after school?  ",
        "answer": " The two girls, Sophie and Jansie, were already destined for a job in the biscuit factory and it was likely that they would work there after school."
    },
    {
        "question": "Does Geoff believe what Sophie says about her meeting with Danny Casey?  ",
        "answer": "No, Geoff does not believe what Sophie says about her meeting. He calls it “the unlikeliest thing [he] ever heard”"
    },
    {
        "question": "How would you describe the character and temperament of Sophie’s father?",
        "answer": "Sophie's father has a plumpy face looking grimy and sweaty. He doesn't seem to be a soft or sophisticated man. Sophie fears his aggressive manliness. He is a realist and does not believe in his daughter's wild stories."
    }


]

let start = document.getElementById('start')
let show=  document.getElementById('display')


start.addEventListener('click',()=>{
    let userInput = document.getElementById('inputq').value
    let item = Flamingo.filter(item=>item.question.toLowerCase().includes(userInput));

    dataOutput(item,show)
    contAgain()
 })